var STRINGS =
    {
        "accountPage": {
            "numberUnverified": "Number Unverified",
            "saveCaption": "save"
        },
        "addAnswer":
        {
            "addCaption": "add",
            "noLocations": "Enter a location.",
            "cancel": "Cancel",
            "checkCaption": "check",
            "addLocation": "Add a new location",
            "locationNameCaption": "name",
            "locationAddressCaption": "address (be specific)",
            "locationLinkCaption": "link (optional)",
            "locationNotFound": "Address not found",
            "locationPhoneCaption": "phone (optional)",
            "locationExamples": {
                "caption": "Examples:",
                "example1": "524 12th St, 95814",
                "example2": "Corner of 7th & J Street, Sacramento CA",
                "example3": "Winn Park, Sacramento CA 95816"
            }
        },
        "ageDay": "day",
        "ageDays": "days",
        "ageHour": "hour",
        "ageHours": "hours",
        "ageMinute": "min",
        "ageMinutes": "mins",
        "ageNow": "now",
        "android": "Android",
        "answerHeader": "answers",
        "answerLabel": "enter a location...",
        "answerPage": {
            "directionsLocation": "urbanAsk needs to access your location to get directions.<br /><br />"
                + "Is this OK?<br /><br />"
                + "Your device may also ask permission."
        },
        "answerPosted": "Posted",
        "backButtonAnswer": "Answer",
        "backButtonQuestion": "Question",
        "backButtonQuestions": "Questions",
        "backButtonTopUsers": "Top Users",
        "backButtonUser": "User",
        "cancelButtonCaption": "cancel",
        "checkmark": "&#10004;",
        "contact":
        {
            "call": "call",
            "website": "website",
            "googleMaps": "Google Maps"
        },
        "createAccount":
        {
            "cancelAccount": "cancel",
            "saveAccount": "create"
        },
        "dateFormat": "%m %d, %y",
        "distanceHere": "here",
        "distanceKm": "km",
        "distanceMeters": "m",
        "distanceMiles": "mi",
        "distanceFeet": "ft",
        "edit":
        {
            "addContact": "add urbanAsk to contacts",
            "phoneNumberCaption": "I want to be able to ask questions by sending a text message:",
            "phoneNumberPlaceholder": "mobile # (ex: +14156305242)",
            "usernameCaption": "username",
            "taglineCaption": "tagline",
            "regionCaption": "In addition to questions near me, show me the following region",
            "regionNone": "&lt;none&gt;"
        },
        "editAccountCaption": "settings",
        "emailLabel": "email",
        "error":
        {
            "answerSelect": "There was an error saving your selection.",
            "answerVote": "There was an error saving your vote.",
            "contactAdded": "There was an error adding the contact.",
            "deleteAnswer": "There was an error deleting your question.",
            "geoLocation": "Could not determine your location. Verify that location services are enabled on your device for urbanAsk.",
            "loadAccount": "There was an error loading your account information.",
            "loadTopUsers": "There was an error loading top users.",
            "loadQuestion": "There was an error loading this question.",
            "loadQuestions": "There was an error loading the questions.",
            "loadRegions": "There was an error loading regions.",
            "loadUser": "There was an error loading this user.",
            "noAnswersToSelect": "There are no answers to select.",
            "questionLocationNotFound": "Location '%1' not found. Check your spelling or be more specific.",
            "saveAnswer": "There was an error saving this answer.",
            "saveQuestion": "There was an error saving this question.",
            "saveQuestionUpvote": "There was an error saving your vote.",
            "voteOnOwnQuestion": "You can't vote on your own question.",
            "voteOnOwnAnswer": "You can't vote on your own answer."
        },
        "existingAnswer": "Existing Answer",
        "externalFooter": "Available on: ",
        "facebook": {
            "authenticatingCaption": "Authenticating...",
            "loginCaption": "Login with Facebook",
            "openGraphComment": "found this at %1 (%2).",
            "openGraphAnswerAsComment": "suggested %1 (%2).",
            "postQuestionToFacebook": "Post Question",
            "postQuestionToTwitter": "Tweet Question",
            "postFacebookMessageCaption": "optional message",
            "postCaption": "post"
        },
        "headerBadges": "badges",
        "instructions": {
            "tap": "tap",
            "click": "click",
            "postQuestion": "Type something you're looking for here.",
            "postQuestionSend": "Then %1 here to send it.",
            "tryItNow": "Try it now!",
            "viewQuestions": "This is what people around you are looking for.",
            "viewMyQuestions": "Anything you're looking for will be up top.",
            "viewQuestion": "To add an answer, %1 a question.",
            "viewQuestionWho": "This is who is looking.",
            "viewQuestionWhat": "This is what they want.",
            "viewQuestionWhere": "This is where they want it.",
            "viewAnswer": "Answers to this question are here.",
            "addAnswer": "To add an answer, %1 here.",
            "toolbarQuestions": "To view questions, %1 here.",
            "toolbarTop": "To view the leaderboard, %1 here.",
            "toolbarUser": "To view your profile, %1 here."
        },
        "intervalDayCaption": "day",
        "intervalWeekCaption": "week",
        "intervalMonthCaption": "month",
        "intervalYearCaption": "year",
        "intervalAllCaption": "all",
        "iphone": "iPhone",
        "letters": "ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ",
        "login":
        {
            "createEmailAccount": "Signup with Email",
            "loginMobile": "Signup with Mobile #",
            "twitter": "Login with Twitter",
            "loginRequired": "You must login to %1.<br /><br />Would you like to login now?",
            "loginRequiredAction": 
            {
                "askQuestion": "ask a question",
                "profile": "view your profile",
                "addAnswer": "add an answer",
                "deleteAnswer": "delete an answer",
                "selectAnswer": "select an answer",
                "vote": "vote"    
            },
            "verifyMobile": "You'll receive a text soon to verify your mobile number."
        },
        "local": "local",
        "months": ["Jan", "Feb", "Mar", "Apr", "May", "Jun", "Jul", "Aug", "Sep", "Oct", "Nov", "Dec"],
        "mobileNumber": "mobile # (ex: +14156305242)",
        "multiplication": "&#215;",
        "notificationAskQuestion": "?",
        "notificationAnswerQuestion": "@",
        "notificationReputation": "+%1 reputation",
        "notificationDownvote": "-1",
        "notificationUpvote": "+1",
        "notification":
        {
            "answerSaved": "answer posted",
            "contactAdded": "urbanAsk was added to your contacts",
            "contactUpdated": "The urbanAsk contact has been updated",
            "contactExists": "The urbanAsk contact already exists",
            "downloading": "downloading...",
            "newVersion": "There is a new version of urbanAsk.",
            "postedToFacebook": "Successfully posted to your wall.",
            "questionSaved": "question saved",
            "savingQuestion": "saving question..."
        },
        "okButtonCaption": "ok",
        "optionalNote": "optional note...",
        "passwordLabel": "password",
        "questionHeader": "questions",
        "questionLabel": "Where can I find...",
        "questionPage": {

            "addNewAnswerCaption": "Add an Answer"

        },
        "questionPosted": "Posted",
        "questionsNearby": "nearby",
        "questionsPage": {

            "askQuestionLocation": "urbanAsk needs to access your location to post this question.<br /><br />"
                + "Is this OK?<br /><br />"
                + "Your device may also ask permission.",
            "viewNearbyQuestions": "view questions near me",
            "nearbyQuestionsInstructions": "urbanAsk needs access to your location to display questions near you.<br /><br />"
                + "Is this OK?<br /><br /> Your device may also ask permission."

        },
        "questionsEverywhere": "everywhere",
        "rightAngleBracket": "&#9002;",
        "toolbar":
        {
            "questions": "questions",
            "top": "top",
            "profile": "profile"
        },
        "topTypeReputationCaption": "reputation",
        "topTypeQuestionsCaption": "questions",
        "topTypeAnswersCaption": "answers",
        "topTypeBadgesCaption": "badges",
        "topUsers":
        {
            "everywhere": "everywhere",
            "noTopUsers": "No one in your area has %1 %2 <br /><br />Why not be the first?",
            "noTopUsersType": ["earned any reputation", "asked any questions", "answered any questions", "earned any badges"],
            "noTopUsersInterval": ["yet.", "today.", "this week.", "this month.", "this year."]
        },
        "reputation": "reputation",
        "totalAnswers": "answers",
        "totalAnswersOne": "answer",
        "totalBadges": "badges",
        "totalBadgesOne": "badge",
        "totalQuestions": "questions",
        "totalQuestionsOne": "question",
        "userIdCaption": "id",
        "user":
        {
            "memberSince": "signup",
            "noAnswersMe": "You have not answered any questions yet. <br /><br />Go help someone find something.",
            "noAnswersUser": "%1 has not answered any questions yet.",
            "noBadgesMe": "You have not earned any badges yet. <br /><br />You're missing out!",
            "noBadgesUser": "%1 has not earned any badges yet.",
            "noQuestionsMe": "You have not asked any questions yet. <br /><br />Looking for something?",
            "noQuestionsUser": "%1 has not asked any questions yet.",
            "noReputationMe": "You have not earned any reputation yet. <br /><br />Get started!",
            "noReputationUser": "%1 has not earned any reputation yet.",
            "notifications": "notifications"
        },
        "usernameLabel": "username",
        "versionCaption": "version: ",
        "voteDownCaption": "-1",
        "voteUpCaption": "+1",
        "xmark": "&#10008;",
        "xmarkDelete": "&times;"
    };